<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Emergency Communication System</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="language_preference">Language Preference</string>
    <string name="profile_and_settings">Profile &amp; Settings</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="receive_notifications">Receive Notifications</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="about_app_content">This is the Emergency Communication System application. Its purpose is to provide users with critical alerts, reliable communication channels, and quick access to emergency services. This application is designed for educational purposes and should not be relied upon for real emergencies.</string>
    <string name="emergency_dashboard">Emergency Dashboard</string>
    <string name="dashboard_subtitle">Built by Students, for the Community</string>
    <string name="emergency_call_label">EMERGENCY</string>
    <string name="call_button">CALL</string>
    <string name="report_incident">Report Incident</string>
    <string name="i_am_safe">I Am Safe</string>
    <string name="gps_signal_lost">GPS signal lost. Ensure location is on.</string>
    <string name="feels_like">Feels Like</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="wind">Wind</string>
    <string name="visibility">Visibility</string>
    <string name="weather_widget_message">Visibility is low due to current conditions. Drive slowly and stay alert. The humidity is high, so expect some stickiness.</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="alerts">Alerts</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">This is a placeholder for the privacy policy. You should replace this with your own privacy policy.</string>
    <!-- Language settings -->
    <string name="language_settings_title">Choose Language</string>
    <string name="language_settings_back">Back</string>
    <string name="language_settings_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>
    <string name="language_filipino">Filipino</string>
    <string name="language_spanish">Spanish</string>
    <!-- Weather advice -->
    <string name="weather_advice_feels_much_hotter">It feels much hotter than the actual temperature.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_feels_much_cooler">It feels much cooler than the actual temperature.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_humidity_high">The humidity is high, so expect some stickiness.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_wind_strong">Winds are quite strong, so be careful of flying debris.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_wind_breezy">It’s a bit breezy.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_visibility_low">Visibility is low. Be extra careful when driving or walking.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_clear_1">It’s a bright, sunny day. A great time for outdoor plans—just don’t forget sunscreen and stay hydrated.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_clear_2">Clear skies today! Perfect for going out, but the sun might get strong later, so stay protected.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_clouds_1">The sky is cloudy. The temperature might drop a bit, so a light jacket could be a good idea.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_clouds_2">It’s looking overcast. No rain yet, but keep an eye on the sky.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_rain_1">It’s raining. Roads can get slippery, so move carefully and carry an umbrella or raincoat.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_rain_2">Expect rainfall. Make sure you’re prepared with waterproof gear and take extra caution.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_drizzle_1">A light drizzle is happening. It’s manageable, but you might want a jacket to stay dry.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_drizzle_2">Expect some light rain. Nothing heavy, but enough to make things damp.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_thunderstorm_1">A thunderstorm is expected. It’s best to stay indoors and avoid open areas.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_thunderstorm_2">Thunderstorms incoming. Postpone outdoor plans and stay updated on alerts.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_snow_1">Snow is falling. Dress warmly and be cautious—roads can be slippery.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_snow_2">Expect snowy conditions. Bundle up and travel carefully if you need to go out.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_low_visibility_1">Visibility is low due to current conditions. Drive slowly and stay alert.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_low_visibility_2">Low-visibility weather detected. Travel can be risky, so please be careful.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_unusual_1">The weather seems unusual today. Keep an eye on updates and stay prepared.</string>
    <string name="weather_advice_unusual_2">Conditions are a bit unpredictable. It’s best to stay alert and ready for anything.</string>
</resources>